Finding Aid for the Collection of Tract Maps and Cadastral Maps of Southern California LSC.0349
UCLA Library Special Collections
Collection of Tract Maps and Cadastral Maps of Southern California
1868-1937
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0349
5 oversize folders
The tract and cadastral maps in this collection are of real estate developments located in Los Angeles, Orange, Riverside and Ventura counties. The maps are listed by location using the Thomas Brothers Maps' Los Angeles County Popular Street Atlas, 1931 and Orange County, 1981. A few maps fall outside of this territory, and for these, relevant leaves of the Thomas ... Riverside County, 1978, and Ventura County, 1979, have been included.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942328873606533
History
Tract maps present certain problems in indexing or cataloging since they do not all have a common element such as a name or a cartographer. The approach, therefore, that seems most logical is to list the maps by location. The locator used by the Cadastral Map Collection is the Thomas Brothers Maps' Los Angeles County Popular Street Atlas, 1931 and Orange County, 1981. A few maps fall outside of this territory, and for these, eleven leaves of the Thomas ... Riverside County, 1978, and Ventura County, 1979, have been included. The location is designated by atlas page number and grid coordinates (the area where the letters printed across the top of the page intersect the numbers printed down the side). This location designation has been used as the call number of individual maps.
There are various ways of approaching this collection. If the name of a tract is known, it is listed alphabetically in the finding aid. In addition, there are chronological and location (call) number lists. Few maps have all of these elements. If the location of the tract map is all that is known, the Thomas Atlas must be checked to find a location designation. The finding aid must then be consulted to see if a map exists for that location.
When more than one tract appears on a map, each tract has been given its own location designation. The first such location designation has been used for the call number and all other tracts have bee cited with a see reference to that number.
Where information about the owner or realtor is available, it has been included in the finding aid.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of tract and cadastral maps of real estate developments, some projected but never realized, located in Los Angeles and vicinity. Most tracts are located in Los Angeles and Orange counties, but some are in Riverside and Ventura counties. Tracts are listed alphabetically, chronologically, and by location (call) number in the finding aid.
Organization and Arrangement
Collection is arranged alphabetically by name of tract.
Related Material
A Collection of Tract Maps From a Real Estate Business Scrapbook, Los Angeles (Collection 295). Available at the UCLA Library Special Collections.
General note
The Thomas Brothers Map of Los Angeles County, 1981 is to be used in conjunction with this finding aid.
Online Items Available
Portions of this collection have been digitized and are available online: Tract Maps and Cadastral Maps of Southern California (9 items).
The same digitized objects and are available through the Calisphere portal: Tract Maps and Cadastral Maps of Southern California (9 items).
Index of Tractmaps with Dates
Mott Tract 1868-69
San Fernando, Town of 1874(?)
San Fernando, Town of 1874(?)
San Juan By-The-Sea 1878
Sausal Redondo Rancho, Map of the Southern Part of 1884
Alcantara Grove Tract 1886
Wiliamson Tract 1886
Rancho Potrero De Felipe Lugo 1886
Rancho Potrero De Felipe Lugo 1886
Diamond Street Tract 1887
Lakeside Tract 1887
University Tract (University of Southern California), The 1887
University Tract (University of Southern California), The 1887
Port Ballona 1887
Claremont 1887
Bardsdale Tract, R.G. Surdam's Plot of the 1887
Forster's Addition to San Juan Capistrano 1888
Lankershim Ranch 1888
Lankershim Ranch 1888
Redondo Beach 1888
Redondo Beach 1888
Willmore, Official Plat of the Town of 1880s
Rancho La Ballona 1880s
Playa Del Rey 1880s(?)
Centinella Rancho 1880s(?)
Inglewood 1880s(?)
Sausal Redondo Rancho 1880s(?)
Los Angeles Trust Company 1880s(?)
Walnut and Bean Land Company 1880s(?)
Golden Gate Tract 1891
Child's Heights 1891(?)
Wolfskill Tract 1893
Adams Street Tract 1894
Westmoreland Place and Tract 1902
Westmoreland Place and Tract 1902
Garfield Heights 1904(?)
Beverly Hills, Portion of 1906
Commonwealth Terrace 1910
Commonwealth Terrace 1910
Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands 1910
Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands 1910
Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands 1910
Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands 1910
Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands 1910
Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands 1910
Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands 1910
Van Nuys 1910
Marian, Town of 1910
Owensmouth, Town of 1910
Granada Place 1911
South Porter Tracts 1911
Keifer Tract 1911
Hiscock and Smith's First Addition 1911
M.L. Wicks Subdivision of Carbolino Cooper 1911
Exposition Park Square, Mitchel's 1911-12
Exposition Park Square, Mitchel's 1911-12
Palisades, The 1912
Hollenbeck Heights Tract 1912
Seaside Terrace 1912
El Segundo, Official Map of 1912
Inglewood Acres 1912
West Adams and Washington Boulevard Tract 1912
El Segundo, Official Map of 1912-13
El Segundo, Official Map of 1912-13
Washington Park 1912(?)
Los Angeles, Business Property Map of 1913
Los Angeles, Business Property Map of 1913
Inglewood 1913
Hill Acreage 1913
Inglewood Acreage 1913
Hyde Park Acreage 1913
Hill Acreage 1913
Tract no. 215 1913
Baldwin Acreage 1913
Baldwin 500 Acres 1913
College Site Acreage 1913
Keating Acreage 1913
New College Tract 1913
Tract 1700 1913
St. Vincent College Tract 1913
Western Avenue Square 1913
Kendall's Berry Tract 1913
Derby Park Tract 1913
Los Angeles Investment Cos House Factory and Yards 1913
Bagley Tract 1913
Hollywood 1913
Hollywood 1913
Colegrove 1913
Ivanhoe 1913
Elysian Park 1913
Hill Street Lot 1913
Olive Street Lot 1913
Broadway Lot 1913
Deeble Tract 1913
Elder Place no. 1 1913
Butler and Elder Tract 1913
Elder Place no. 2 1913
Rancho Sausal Redondo 1913
Rodgers Park Tract--no. 1356 1913
Rodgers Park Tract--no. 715 1913
Loretta Park Tract 1913
Figueroa Park Square Tract 1913
Ivywild 1913(?)
Harbor City 1914
Untitled. 1914(?)
Normal Place 1915
Huos Tract (no. 6256) 1923
Seventh council District, New 1929
Seventh council District, New 1929
Seventh council District, New 1929
Seventh council District, New 1929
Seventh council District, New 1929
Overhill Unit 1929
Malis Tract 37 Oil Syndicate 1920s(?)
Burbank-Western Portion 1933
Burbank-Western Portion 1933
Alhambra, City of 1937
Alhambra, City of 1937
Alhambra, City of 1937
Alhambra, City of 1937
Alhambra, City of 1937
Avalon, city of--Blocks 1-24 (Santa Catalina Isl) 1937
California, Southern -- Maps.; Real property -- Maps.; Land subdivision -- California, Southern.
- A.H. Busch Tract., LA 43 F, 2. (Box 1)
- Abbot and Margaret Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
  General note
  See: LA 44 A-D, 1-6.
- Abbot Kinney Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Acacia Tract (no. 1045)., LA 43 E, 1. (Box 1)
- Acantara Grove Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Adams Street Tract, 1894.; LA 52 C, 1. (Folder 5)
- Alcantara Grove Tract, 1886.; LA 44 B, 6. (Box 1)
- Alhambra Acres., LA 37 C, 4-5. (Box 3)
- Alhambra, City of, 1937.; LA 36 F, 3-6.
- Alhambra, City of, 1937.; LA 46 A-B, 1-2.
  See: LA 36 F, 3-6.
- Alhambra, City of, 1937.; LA 45 E-F, 1-2.
- Alhambra, City of, 1937.; LA 37 A-D, 3-6. (Folder 2)
- Alvarado Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Angeles Mesa., LA 51 B-C, 3-4. (Folder 5)
- Angeles Mesa, Map of., LA 51 B-D, 3-4. (Box 1)
- Arcadia Tract., LA 49 A-B, 1-2.
  See: LA 40 E-F, 5-6.
- Arlington Heights Extension., LA 43 C, 4. (Box 3)
- Artesia Tract., LA 41 C-D, 3-4.
- Austin Heights., LA 41 B-C, 6.
- Austin Heights., LA 49 B, 1.
- Avalon, City of--Blocks 1-24 (Santa Catalina Island), 1937.; LA 77 B, 5. (Folder 4)
- Bagley Tract, 1913.; LA 51 D-E, 2-4.
  See: LA 51 A, 6.
- Baldwin 500 Acres, 1913.; LA 51 A-C, 1-3.
- Baldwin Acreage, 1913.; LA 51 A-C, 1-3.
- Baldwin's Subdivision., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Bandini Tract., LA 49 A-B, 1-2.
- Banfit Villa., LA C-E, 4.
- Bardsdale Tract, R.G. Surdam's Plot of the., VE 42 A-E, 1-2.
  See: VE 31 B-E, 5-6.
- Bardsdale Tract, R.G. Surdam's Plot of the, 1887.; VE 31 B-E, 5-6. (Folder 6)
- Beck Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Bellevue Terrace Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Bell's Addition Subdivision., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Bentley and Cuppeno Fourth Street Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Beverly Hills, Portion of, 1906.; LA 33 B, 5-6. (Folder 2)
- Boehm Addition., LA 41 A-C, 4-5.
- Bonito Tract, The., LA 43 E, 4.
- Bonnie Brae Tract., LA 44 B, 2.
- Boutons Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Bravender Tract., LA 34 C, 3-4.
- Brentwood Park., LA 41 A-B, 1-3.
- Brentwood Terrace., LA 41 A-B, 1-3.
- Briswalter Tract., LA 52 C-D, 1. (Folder 5)
- Broadway Lot [Olive/Hill/Broadway], 1913.; LA 44 C, 3-4. (Box 8)
- Brodericks Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Brooklyn Heights., LA 45 C-D, 3-4. (Folder 4)
- Brown and Adams Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Bruning Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Bunker Hill Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Burbank-Western Portion, 1933.; LA 24 A-D, 1-3.
  See: LA 17 A-D, 4-6.
- Burbank-Western Portion, 1933.; LA 17 A-D, 4-6. (Box 8)
- Burton Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Bush Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Butler and Elder Tract, 1913.; LA 52 D-F, 1-2.
- Cambridge Tract., LA 41 C-D, 3-4.
- Cameron Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Canyon Castle Park., LA 33 E, 1. (Folder 2)
- Carlos Heights., LA 41 A-B, 1-3.
- Carr Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Castle Garden., LA 41 C-D, 3-4.
- Centinella Rancho, (?)., 1880s; LA 56 A-F, 1-5.
  See: LA 55A D-F, 1-5.
- Central Addition., LA 49 A-B, 1-2.
- Child's Heights, (?)., 1891; LA 35 A, 4. (Folder 2)
- Ciningham Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- City Centre Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- City Park and Lake Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Claremont, 1887.; LA 91 B-C, 3-4. (Folder 4)
- Clarence Tract., LA 41 C-E, 4.
- Clen-nar Heights., LA 41 A-C, 4-5.
- Cliffton Acres., LA 67 D-E, 5-6.
- Cliffton By the Sea., LA 67 D-E, 5-6. (Box 3)
- Cliffton Heights., LA 67 D-E, 5-6.
- Cohn Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Colegrove., LA 34 C, 4. (Folder 2)
- Colegrove., LA 34 C, 3-4. (Folder 2)
- Colegrove, 1913.; LA 34 A-C, 4-6. (Folder 2)
- Colina Park., LA 44 B, 2.
- College Site Acreage, 1913.; LA 51 A-C, 1-3.
- Commonwealth Terrace, 1910.; LA 44 A, 1-2.
  See: LA 43 F, 1-2.
- Commonwealth Terrace, 1910.; LA 43 F, 1-2. (Box 3)
- Country Club Park., LA 43 D, 2-3. (Box 3)
- Cox Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Cranis Replat., LA 41 C-D, 3-4.
- Crawford Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Crosier Addition., LA 41 A-C, 4-5.
- Davis Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Davis Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- DeCelis Vineyard Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Deeble Tract, 1913.; LA 52 C-F, 1-2.
- Dennis and Stewart Addition., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Derby Park Tract, 1913.; LA 51 D-E, 2-4.
- Diamond Street Tract, 1887.; LA 35 A, 6. (Folder 2)
- Downey Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Dunigan Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Dunkelberger Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Durley Park Tract., LA 49 D, 2. (Folder 5)
- E.H. Workman Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- East Ocean Park Tract., LA 49 F, 1.
  See: ***G1529 L8R83a 1902.
- East Ocean Park Villa Tract, Map of., LA 49 F, 1.
- El Segundo, Official Map of, 1912-13.; LA 56 A-C, 5-6. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  See: LA 55A F, 5-6.
- El Segundo, Official Map of, 1912-13.; LA 55A F, 5-6. (Folder 7)
- El Segundo, Official Map of, 1912.; LA 56 A-C, 5-6.
- Elder Place no. 1, 1913.; LA 52 D-F, 1-2.
- Elder Place no. 2, 1913.; LA 52 D-F, 1-2.
- Eleventh Street Block., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Ellis Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Elysian Park, 1913.; LA 35 D-E, 4-5.
- Elysian Gardens. Number Two Tract 3416 California Home Extension Association 728 South Hill Street, Ground Floor, Los Angeles. (Box 3)
  General
  Opening Distribution Annoucement We are now ready to show your our wonderful " Little Farms by th River" within walking distance of many jobs; twenty minutes by 5c car from Sixth and Hill Streets at $180 to $290 for regular 40 foot lots also acres and half acres.
- Erkenbrecher Syldiczie Santa Monica Tract., LA 41 B-C, 6.
- Exposition Park Square, Mitchel's, 1911-12.; LA 52 A, 2.
  See: LA 51 F, 2.
- Exposition Park Square, Mitchel's, 1911-12.; LA 51 F, 2. (Folder 5)
- F.P. Howard Subdivision., LA 49 A-B, 1-2.
- Fairfax Park Tract., LA 42 E-F, 2-3. (Box 1)
- Fairfax View Tract., LA 44 B, 2.
- Figueroa Park Square Tract, 1913.; LA 58 A, 1.
- Figueroa Street Square., LA 58 A, 1. (Box 1)
- Forman Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
  See: LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Forster's Addition to San Juan Capistrano, 1888.; OR 36 B-C, 5-6. (Folder 6)
- Fort Hill Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Francisco Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Fraser and Jones' Strand Tract., LA 49 B-C, 4-5.
- Freemont Tract., LA 34 C, 3-4.
- Friends Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Galpin Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Gano's Subdivision, Avalon--Santa Catalina Island., LA 77 B, 5. (Box 1)
- Garey Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Garey Tract Addition., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Garfield Heights, (?)., 1904; LA 43 D, 4. (Box 1)
- Gate Acres., LA 41 A-B, 1-3.
- Gillis Subdivision., LA 41 C-E, 4.
- Golden Bay Tract., LA 49 B, 3-4.
- Golden Gate Tract, 1891.; LA 35 B, 4. (Box 1)
- Goldworthy Eighth Street Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Gotham Park., LA 58 B, 1. (Box 3)
- Gracewood Tract., LA 34 C, 3-4.
- Granada Place, 1911.; LA 45 F, 1. (Folder 4)
- Green Acres., LA 41 A-C, 4-5.
- Greenwell Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Grove Orchard Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6. (Box 4)
- Harbor City, 1914.; LA 73 E-F, 2-3.
- Harvey Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Heffner and Irvine Subdivision., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Hege Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Hemet., RI 88 C-F, 1-6.
- Hemet., RI 89 A-B, 1-6.
  See: RI 88 C-F, 1-6.
- Hermosa Beach., LA 67 B-C, 1-2.
  See: LA 62 B-C, 5-6.
- Hermosa Beach., LA 62 B-C, 5-6. (Folder 4)
- Highland Tract., LA 49 A-B, 1-2.
- Hill Acreage, 1913.; LA 51 A, 4-5.
- Hill Acreage, 1913.; LA 51 B, 5.
- Hill Street Lot, 1913.; LA 44 C, 3-4.
- Hillcrest Tract., LA 49 A-B, 1-2.
- Hiscock and Smith's First Addition, 1911.; LA 44 E, 5.
- Hodge Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Hollenbeck Heights Tract, 1912.; LA 45 C, 6. (Box 1)
- Hollywood, 1913.; LA 33 E-F, 4-6.
- Hollywood, 1913.; LA 34 A-C, 4-6.
- Hollywood New Addition, Morgan's., LA 34 D, 3. (Folder 2)
- Hoover Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Howard Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Huba Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Huos Tract (no. 6256), 1923.; LA 42 E, 4-5. (Box 1)
- Hyde Park Acreage, 1913.; LA 51 B, 5.
- Inglewood, (?)., 1880s; LA 56 A-F, 1-5.
- Inglewood, 1913.; LA 51 A, 6. (Folder 5)
- Inglewood Acreage, 1913.; LA 51 B, 5.
- Inglewood Acres, 1912.; LA 57 B-C, 3-4. (Box 3)
- Inglewood, Town of., LA 51 A-B, 5-6. (Box 1)
- Ivanhoe, 1913.; LA 35 B, 2-3.
- Ivywild, (?)., 1913; LA 42 C, 5. (Folder 6)
- James Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Jefferson Street Park Tract., LA 43 D, 6.
- John C. Downey., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Josefa Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Judson Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Jurupa Rancho., RI 11 A-F, 1-2.
  See: RI 5 A-F, 2-6.
- Jurupa Rancho., RI 5 A-F, 2-6.
- Jurupa Rancho., RI 12 A-B, 1-2.
- Jurupa Rancho., RI 6 A-B, 2-6.
- Keating Acreage, 1913.; LA 51 A-C, 1-3.
- Keifer Tract, 1911.; LA 44 E, 5.
- Kendall's Berry Tract, 1913.; LA 51 D-E, 2-4.
- Kennedy Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Kenwood., LA 58 A, 2. (Box 1)
- Kerckhoff Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Kincaid Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Kinney Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Los Angeles Trust Company, (?)., 1880s; LA 56 A-F, 1-5.
- Lake Shore Tract., LA 44 B, 2.
- Lakeside Tract, 1887.; LA 35 C, 5-6. (Folder 7)
- Lanahl and Spitly Subdivision., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Lander Tract., LA 34 C, 3-4.
- Lankershim Ranch, 1888.; LA 16 B-F, 1-4.
- Lankershim Ranch, 1888.; LA 9 B-F, 1-6. (Folder 7)
- Long Beach, City of., LA 75 B-D, 4-6. (Box 1)
- Longstreet Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Loomis and Cole Tract., LA 41 C-D, 3-4.
- Loop and Meserve Tract., LA 90 E-F, 4.
  See: LA 94 E-F, 2-3.
- Loretta Park Tract, 1913.; LA 51 E-F, 5-6.
- Los Angeles--Holdings Map., LA 44 C, 3-4.
- Los Angeles Homestead Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Los Angeles Investment Cos House Factory and Yards, 1913.; LA 51 D-E, 2-4.
- Los Angeles, Business Property Map of, 1913.; LA 44 B, 4-5. (Box 8)
- Los Angeles, Business Property Map of, 1913.; LA 44 C-D, 2-4.
  See: LA 44 B, 4-5.
- Los Angeles, Downtown., LA 44 C, 3-4.
- Los Angeles, Downtown., LA 44 D, 2-3.
  See: LA 44 C, 3-4.
- Lucas Tract., LA 49 A-B, 1-2.
- M.L. Wicks Subdivision of Carbolino Cooper, 1911.; LA 44 E, 5. (Box 3)
- Magdalena Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Malis Tract 37 Oil Syndicate, (?)., 1920s; OR 26 A-F, 5-6. (Folder 6)
- Manasquan Tract., LA 34 C, 3-4.
- Marengo Tract., LA 37 A-B, 1-3. (Box 1)
- Marian, Town of, 1910.; LA 14 A-F, 3-6.
  See: LA 12 A-F, 3-6.
- Mariposa Tract., LA 36 D, 5. (Box 3)
- Martin Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Marvin Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- McDonald Tract, Map of the (Rancho San Pedro)., LA 63 A-D, 4-5. (Folder 4)
- McLaughlin Subdivision., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Merriam, March and Gardner Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Mese La Ballano., LA 49 E, 1-2.
- Meyer Block., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Michillinda., LA 28 B, 5. (Box 1)
- Millars Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Mills Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Mills Subdivision., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Mission Courts., LA 37 E, 4. (Box 3)
- Morris Vineyard Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Mott Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3. (Box 1)
- Mott Tract, 1868-69.; LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Mueller Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Murat Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- National Boulevard Heights., LA 41 E-F, 6. (Box 1)
- Nettelson's Subdivision of Ellis Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- New College Tract, 1913.; LA 51 D-E, 2-4.
- Newell and Rider Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Nichols Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Niles Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Nordholt Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Normal Place, 1915.; LA 34 F, 4. (Box 1)
- North Pomona Tract., LA 91 B-C, 4-5.
- O.W. Child's Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Ocean Park Heights., LA 49 E-F, 1-2.
- Ocean Park Heights., LA 41 E, 6.
- Ocean Park Tract., LA 49 F, 1-2.
- Ocean Park Tract., LA 50 A, 3.
- Ocean Park Villa Tract., LA 49 C, 3.
- Oceanside Villa Tract., LA 62 C, 4. (Folder 4)
- Olive Street Lot, 1913.; LA 44 C, 3-4.
- O'Neil Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Orchard Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Overhill Unit, 1929.; LA 50 F, 4. (Box 1)
- Owens and Scott Subdivision., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Owensmouth, Town of, 1910.; LA 12 A-F, 3-6.
- Pacific Farms., LA 41 C-E, 4.
- Pallisades., LA 40 E-F, 5-6. (Box 1)
- Pallisades, The, 1912.; LA 40 E-F, 5. (Box 1)
- Palm Place., LA 42 B-C, 1-2. (Box 3)
- Paloma Terrace., LA 58 F, 4-5. (Box 3)
- Palomares Tract., LA 90 E-F, 3.
- Pama Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Paradise Tract., LA 41 A-C, 4-5.
- Park Villa Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Pedley., RI 5 E-F, 5-6.
- Pierce Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Platers Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Playa Del Rey, (?)., 1880s; LA 55A D-F, 1-5.
- Pomona and Vicinity, Map of., LA 94 E-F, 2-3. (Box 1)
- Grand Exursion Pomona! Special Auction Sale! Easton & Eldridg, Auctioneers. The Palomares Tract in Beautiful Villa Plots, of one to five acre parcels, AsloTown Lots and Blocks, Saturday, Feb. 12, 1887. (Box 1)
  Los Angeles Land Bureau, G. W. Fink, President, 20 West First Street.
- Port Ballona, 1887.; LA 49 C-E, 4-6. (Folder 6)
- Prager Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Prospect Hill Addition., LA 49 A-B, 1-2.
- Pryor Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Rafferty Pendleton Sub.., LA 27 D-E, 4-5. (Folder 2)
- Rampart Heights., LA 44 A, 1. (Box 1,3)
- Rancho Del Mar., LA 49 E, 3.
- Rancho La Ballona, (?)., 1880s; LA 55A D-F, 1-5.
- Rancho Potrero De Felipe Lugo, 1886.; LA 47 E-F, 2-4.
- Rancho Potrero De Felipe Lugo, 1886.; LA 48 A, 2-3.
  See: LA 47 E-F, 2-4.
- Rancho San Vicente, Portion of., LA 41 A, 3-5.
- Rancho Sausal Redondo, 1913.; LA 56 F, 2-3.
- Redondo Beach, 1888.; LA 67 D-E, 4.
  See: LA 67 C-D, 2-3.
- Redondo Beach, 1888.; LA 67 C-D, 2-3.
- Regina Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Requena Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Reyes Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Rodgers Park Tract--no. 1356, 1913.; LA 51 E-F, 5-6.
- Rodgers Park Tract--no. 715, 1913.; LA 51 E-F, 5-6.
- Roseboro Villa Tract., LA 49 F, 2-3.
- Roseborough Heights., LA 49 E, 2.
  See: ***G1528 L8R83a 1902.
- Rowen Tract., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Ruby Tract., LA 41 C-E, 4.
- San Antonio Tract., LA 95 C-D, 1-2.
- San Antonio Tract., LA 91 C-D, 6.
- San Fernando, Town of, (?)., 1874; LA 2 D-E, 5-6. (Box 1)
- San Fernando, Town of, (?)., 1874; LA 8 D-E, 1-2.
  See: LA 2 D-E, 5-6.
- Maclay Colony of San Fernando, of Los Angeles County, California. [ca. 1890]. (Box 1)
  THE MACLAY RANCHO Ex Mission of San Fernando. Trustees: H. L. Macneil, Geo. C. Hagar, C Maclay, J. K. Alexander, R. M. Widney. NOTE: The Blocks numbered from 1 to 402 are divided into four(40 parts by lines runnning parallel to the Streets. These parts are known as the North, East, West and South subdivisions or ___Acres, and are so described in the Deeds.
  R. M. Widney, et al., Trustees, University Bank 317 New High Street, Los Angeles, Cal.
- San Juan By-The-Sea, 1878.; OR 38 A-B, 4-5. (Folder 6)
- San Pedro., LA 78 F, 2-6.
- San Pedro., LA 79 A, 2-6.
- Sanborn Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Santa Anita Oaks. (Folder 2)
- Sausal Redondo Rancho, (?)., 1880s; LA 56 A-F, 1-5.
- Sausal Redondo Rancho, Map of the Southern Part of, 1884.; LA 55A E-F, 4. (Folder 5)
- Sawtelle., LA 41 C-E, 4.
- Schader Addition., LA 41 A-C, 4-5.
- Schiller Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Seagirt., LA 49 C, 3.
- Seagirt Tract, Map of., LA 49 C, 3.
- Seaside Terrace, 1912.; LA 49 A, 2. (Box 3)
- Seaside Terrace (Vicente Terrace Tract on back)., LA 49 A, 2. (Box 3)
- Seventh Council District, New, 1929.; LA 52 A-E, 1-3.
  See: LA 43 D-F, 6.
- Seventh Council District, New, 1929.; LA 44 A-E, 6. (Box 1)
- Seventh Council District, New, 1929.; LA 43 D-F, 6.
- Seventh Council District, New, 1929.; LA 51 D-F, 1-3.
- Seventh Street Addition Tract., LA 43 F, 2. (Box 1)
- Severance Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Shaw Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Sierra Vista Heights., LA 41 A-C, 4-5.
- Sierra Vista Townsite., LA 41 A-C, 4-5.
- Silver Strand., LA 49 B-C, 4-5.
- Sisters of Charity Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- South Porter Tracts, 1911.; LA 44 E, 5.
- Spencer's Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- St. Vincent College Tract, 1913.; LA 51 D-E, 2-4.
- Star Tract., LA 44 A-B, 3-4.
- Stephenson's Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Stil (?) Subdivision., LA 44 C-D, 4-6.
- Sunnymead Orchard Tract., RI 15 B-E, 4-6. (Box 1)
- Sunset, DeLongre, Fountain Cahuanga area, ca. 1914.; LA 34 C, 3-4. (Folder 2)
- Tilden Tract., LA 41 A-C, 4-5.
- Towner Terrace., LA 41 B-C, 6. (Box 1)
- Towner Terrace., LA 49 A-B, 1.
- Tract 1700, 1913.; LA 51 D-E, 2-4.
- Tract no. 215, 1913.; LA 43 A-B, 1.
- Treat Tract., LA 44 A-B, 5-6.
- Truman Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Tucker Langdon Tract., LA 41 C-E, 4.
- University Tract (University of Southern California), The, 1887.; LA 44 A, 6. (Box 1)
  See: LA 43 F, 6.
- University Tract (University of Southern California), The, 1887.; LA 43 F, 6.
- Unnamed., LA 42 F, 5. (Folder 6)
- Unnamed., LA 43 A, 5.
  See: LA 42 F, 5.
- Urquidez Garden Tract., LA 44 C-D, 2-3.
- Van Nuys, 1910.; LA 15 B-F, 3-6.
- Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands, 1910.; LA 15 A-F, 3-6.
- Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands, 1910.; LA 12 A-F, 3-6. (Folder 7)
- Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands, 1910.; LA 23 A-F, 1-2.
- Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands, 1910.; LA 16 A-F, 3-6.
- Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands, 1910.; LA 14 A-F, 3-6.
- Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands, 1910.; LA 21 A-F, 1-2.
- Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands, 1910.; LA 13 A-F, 1-2.
- Van Nuys--Lankershim Lands, 1910.; LA 22 A-F, 1-2.
- Venice., LA 49 B-C, 4.
- Venice--Canals., LA 49 B-C, 4.
- Venice Annex., LA 49 C-D, 3-4.
- Venice Annex no. 1 and no. 2., LA 49 C, 4.
- Venice of America., LA 49 B-C, 4.